(Leonard:)Hey, will you steam my uniform next?
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
Do you recall this conversation?
"Leonard, wanna go halfsies
on a steamer?"
"No, Sheldon, we don't need a steamer."
(Sheldon:)Looks like that rumpled
chicken's come home to roost.
(Penny:)Hi. Here are the makeup
sponges you asked for.
- Oh, thanks, I thought I had more.
- Hmm.
(Penny:)Damn, you've got more makeup than I do.
(Penny:)You've got better makeup than I do.
Yeah, I'm borrowing this.
(Leonard:)Hey, hey, hey,
this is my Comic-Con makeup.
(Leonard:)I love you, but there are some things
a man doesn't share with his girlfriend.
(Sheldon:)That's a wise policy.
(Sheldon:)I once borrowed my sister's makeup
for a costume contest...
...got a terrible case of pink eye.
Yeah, well, luckily, I was going
as a zombie, I won second place.
(Penny:)You guys just went to Comic-Con.
(Leonard:)That was San Diego Comic-Con.
This is Bakersfield Comic-Con.
- Is that better?
- Well, it's a lot smaller.
It's about the comic books.
(Leonard:)The way these conventions used to be
before they went Hollywood.
(Sheldon:)So to answer your question,
no, it's not better.
(Penny:)Then why are you going?
(Sheldon:)It's a comic book convention.
(Sheldon:)Like pizza or particle accelerators...
...even the stinky ones, still pretty good.
(Penny:)Well, you guys have fun.
I guess I'll see you Sunday.
- Yeah. Oh, hang on a second.
- Okay.
(Leonard:)Hold this.
- What was that for?
- To show people when they don't believe me.